export const DivisionQuestion = {
    question1:   {
      question: "10/2 = ?",
      options: [3, 4, 5, 6],
      answer: 5
    },
  question2:  {
      question: "24/3 = ?",
      options: [8, 5, 6, 7],
      answer: 8
    },
   question3: {
      question: "48/3 = ?",
      options: [9, 16, 11, 12],
      answer: 16
    },
   question4: {
      question: "44/4 = ?",
      options: [8, 9, 10, 11],
      answer: 11
    },
  question5:  {
      question: "625/25 = ?",
      options: [10, 25, 12, 13],
      answer: 25
    },
    question6: {
    question: "36/6 = ?",
    options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
    answer: 6
  },
question7: {
    question: "81/9 = ?",
    options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
    answer: 9
  },
question8: {
    question: "100/4 = ?",
    options: [20, 25, 15, 30],
    answer: 25
  },
question9: {
    question: "49/7 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 7
  },
question10: {
    question: "72/8 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 9
  },
question11: {
    question: "120/5 = ?",
    options: [20, 22, 23, 24],
    answer: 24
  },
question12: {
    question: "144/12 = ?",
    options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
    answer: 12
  },
question13: {
    question: "56/7 = ?",
    options: [7, 8, 9, 10],
    answer: 8
  },
question14: {
    question: "90/9 = ?",
    options: [9, 10, 11, 12],
    answer: 10
  },
question15: {
    question: "64/8 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 8
  },
question16: {
    question: "108/9 = ?",
    options: [10, 11, 12, 13],
    answer: 12
  },
question17: {
    question: "125/5 = ?",
    options: [20, 22, 24, 25],
    answer: 25
  },
question18: {
    question: "40/5 = ?",
    options: [6, 7, 8, 9],
    answer: 8
  },
question19: {
    question: "84/12 = ?",
    options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
    answer: 7
  },
question20: {
    question: "56/8 = ?",
    options: [5, 6, 7, 8],
    answer: 7
  }

}

const getRandomQuestions = () => {
  
}